<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Connor Wieseman&#39;s Github Website</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Connor Wieseman&#39;s Github Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The 2020 - 2021 NBA shooting season is more surprising than you think</title>
      <link>/2022/04/08/the-2020-2021-nba-shooting-season-is-more-surprising-than-you-think/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/04/08/the-2020-2021-nba-shooting-season-is-more-surprising-than-you-think/</guid>
      <description>In the game of basketball, the team who scores the most amount of points wins. If a team is good at shooting, they will be able to win a lot of games.
It is a common misconception that defense does not matter in basketball compared to other sports.
The Milwaukee Bucks won the NBA Finals in 2021. They must have been a good shooting team in the playoffs then, right?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Connor Wieseman</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Connor Wieseman, I am a junior at the University of Nebraska - Lincoln. I am double majoring in Journalism and Sports Media and Communication, with a minor in Communication Studies. I am originally from Aurora, Illinois, but moved to Omaha, Nebraska, summer of 2017. After graduation I have two future plans. The first one, being a sports recruiter for either a college or professional sports team. I have experience with meeting and talking to people I never met, as I was a part my fraternity rush team from March 2020 to November 2021.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
