<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Connor Wieseman&#39;s Github Website</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Connor Wieseman&#39;s Github Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What team should win the NBA Finals, based off the regular season? </title>
      <link>/2022/04/21/what-team-should-win-the-nba-finals-based-off-the-regular-season/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/04/21/what-team-should-win-the-nba-finals-based-off-the-regular-season/</guid>
      <description>As of the day this article was posted, most NBA teams that are currently in the playoffs are playing consistent from their regular season performance.
Teams that are expected to win are winning, but that can change at any moment in the playoffs.
Big factors in winning basketball games are shooting, defensive, and the average net rating. Looking off just regular season statistics, we can determine which team is most likely to win the NBA Finals, and compare to their performance in the playoffs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 2020 - 2021 NBA shooting season is more surprising than you think</title>
      <link>/2022/04/08/the-2020-2021-nba-shooting-season-is-more-surprising-than-you-think/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/04/08/the-2020-2021-nba-shooting-season-is-more-surprising-than-you-think/</guid>
      <description>In the game of basketball, the team who scores the most amount of points wins. If a team is good at shooting, they will be able to win a lot of games.
It is a common misconception that defense does not matter in basketball compared to other sports.
The Milwaukee Bucks won the NBA Finals in 2021. They must have been a good shooting team in the playoffs then, right?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
